(Level 1 Demon Lord and One Room Hero)
《Lv1魔王與獨居廢勇者》
(Episode 8: Farewell)
(#8 訣別)
What exactly happened here?
到底發生什麼事
First of all, I need to escape.
先逃出去再說
Zenia,
潔妮亞
humans are not like us demons. They are unable to reawaken from the dead.
人類與我等魔之眷屬不同 無法從死之長眠甦醒過來
Therefore, we must not kill humans without cause. Do you get it?
因此不能濫殺人類 知道嗎
Are you okay? Pull yourself together.
請振作點 還好嗎
The eighth of the seven spy tools, first aid kit.
七大間諜道具之八 急救箱
Don't worry, you will definitely be saved.
不必擔心 一定會得救的
Everyone, please stay away.
請不要靠近
Everyone, please do not crowd around.
麻煩不要圍觀
If I return empty-handed,
空手而回的話
it will harm the demon's reputation.
有損魔之眷屬的名譽
I must bring something.
至少要帶點東西
Anything is fine, but I need to take something back.
什麼都好 要帶收穫回去才行
Oh ya.
對了
Something bad happened, Max.
麥克斯 大事不好了
BREAKING NEWS: UNUSUAL EXPLOSION AT THE MAGIC BUREAU As previously stated, an unusual explosion occurred.
(快訊 魔導廳離奇爆炸) 如剛才所說 今日下午四點
-at 4 p.m. this afternoon. -What happened? Did this just occur now?
-王國魔導廳離奇爆炸 -怎麼搞的 剛才嗎
-Most of the staff have successfully evacuated. -Is this a terrorist attack?
-大部分職員已順利避難 -是不是恐攻
Doesn't Fred work in this building?
弗雷德不是在這棟上班嗎
You don't need to worry about that guy,
用不著擔心那傢伙
he will definitely be unharmed by an explosion of this degree.
這種程度的爆炸 他一定毫髮無傷
I-I see.
這…這樣啊
I actually asked Zenia to investigate the Magic Bureau.
其實朕拜託潔妮亞調查魔導廳
So, is this woman to blame for the explosion?
那麼這場爆炸 該不會是那個女的搞的吧
Why would you say that?
為什麼會這麼說
I didn't ask her to personally go to the Magic Bureau scene,
朕根本沒叫她 親自去魔導廳現場調查
and I certainly didn't ask her to bring a bomb.
更不可能叫她帶炸彈去
I guess you are right.
說得也是
-Mr. Oi. -Yes.
-大井先生 -是
-Okay… yes…
-好…是…
Excuse me, as just mentioned…
不好意思 正如剛才所說…
At four o'clock this afternoon…
今日下午四點…
Shall we watch a variety show?
要不要看綜藝節目
Okay.
好啊
Y-Your majesty…
陛…陛下…
I…am…back…
屬下…回來了…
It stinks.
好臭
Huh?
咦
Have you regained consciousness?
恢復意識了嗎
That's great, you're awake.
太好了 妳醒來了
May I ask who are you?
請問…妳是…
It hurts…
好痛…
Are you okay? Don't push yourself too hard.
還好嗎 不要太勉強自己
You were seriously injured and collapsed at our front door.
妳受了重傷 倒在我們家門口
I recalled it. At that time…
我想起來了 那個時候…
Did I lose consciousness back then?
是在那時失去意識嗎
Why didn't she take me to the hospital? Why did she let me stay here?
但為何不是醫院 而是這種地方
Then you take a good rest.
那妳先多多休息吧
I'll go prepare something to eat right away.
我馬上來準備吃的
This room…
這個房間…
I seem to have seen it somewhere…
似乎在哪裡見過…
Thank you.
謝謝妳
Did you bandage me?
請問是妳幫我包紮的嗎
Yes.
對
Do you live here alone?
妳一個人住這裡嗎
No, I have a husband, but he's away.
不 我有老公 但是他出門了
Is that her work uniform?
是工作服之類的嗎
The hem of that dress is inexplicably short.
那身衣服的下擺莫名短
Do you have anything you want to eat?
有什麼想吃的嗎
I appreciate your kindness, but it is not necessary. I have to go back to work.
不必了 感謝妳的好意 但我必須回去工作了
I'm sorry for leaving.
恕我告辭了
No, you can't move around yet.
不可以 妳還不能亂動
That won't do, I…
那可不行 我…
You rest a little more.
再待久一點
Okay?
好嗎
B-But…
但…但是…
You're young and talented,
如此年輕有為
and you have endless magical power.
源源不絕的魔力
Being a human is such a waste for you.
當人類實在太可惜了
Don't be Fred's subordinate.
別當弗雷德的部下
CONTRACT Why don't you come work for me?
(契約書) 不妨來朕底下工作吧
You can also have seven lives,
妳也可以擁有七條命
two annual bonuses,
一年發兩次獎金
various types of insurance,
各種保險應有盡有
and a generous housing allowance.
而且住宅補貼豐厚
What's your name?
叫什麼名字
I am… Lim…
我叫…琳姆…
Excellent.
好極了
Lim, take my hand.
琳姆 握住朕的手
Join me on the journey to immortal life.
與朕一同邁向不滅之生
Stop it.
住手
What are you doing, Max? This is domestic violence. Domestic violence.
麥克斯你幹什麼 這是家暴耶 家暴
Don't force people to sign improper contracts.
別逼人簽不正當的契約
I shouldn't have left it to you.
果然不該交給你處理
Sign… Contract…
簽名…契約…
I am truly sorry
這一次
this time.
實在是萬分抱歉
So it was on the orders of that long-haired lady
所以是聽了那位長髮小姐的指示
that the bespectacled lady infiltrated the Magic Bureau.
這位眼鏡小姐才會潛入魔導廳
Yes.
沒錯
But it was my initiative to break in.
不過是我自作主張要入侵
I should bear all the responsibility.
該由我負起一切責任
No.
不對
My vague instructions caused this chaos.
是我不該下模糊的指示害她混亂
She is not at fault.
她沒有任何過錯
Anyway,
不論如何
the landlord, Max, had nothing to do with this.
屋主麥克斯完全沒參與這件事
Please be lenient with him.
還請對他高抬貴手
You two are from the demon clan, right?
妳們兩位是魔族 沒錯吧
Yes, indeed.
是的 確實如此
Mr. Max, what exactly is going on?
麥克斯先生 這到底是怎麼回事
Let me explain.
我來說明吧
After the death of the Demon Lord,
魔王大人死後
we, the lower-class servants of the demon, became homeless.
我們這些 魔之眷屬的底層階級無處可歸
We have been living a life of poverty.
一直過著窮困潦倒的生活
We can't fill our stomachs.
填不飽肚子
We can only eat and sleep in the cold.
只能在寒天下餐風露宿
He's blatantly lying.
睜眼說瞎話
It is only fair that we are punished for causing humans trouble.
畢竟給人類添了麻煩 這種報應也是理所當然
But our hearts are actually on the verge of breaking.
然而內心其實已經瀕臨崩潰
But this great hero, Mr. Max,
但這位偉大勇者麥克斯大人
felt sorry for us because we had lost our master
憐憫我們失去了侍奉之主
and took us in.
大發慈悲收留我們
Despite the fact that he despises us and has no obligation to assist the demon.
明明恨之入骨 也沒有義務幫助我們魔之眷屬
Mr. Max's thoughtful heart has deeply moved us.
麥克斯大人的體貼之心 令我們大受感動
We decided to turn a new leaf and live for society, for humanity, from now on.
決定洗心革面 將為了社會 為了人類活下去
Right, Zenia?
對吧 潔妮亞
Right, well said!
對 說得好
We wanted to look into the Magic Bureau
之所以想調查魔導廳
simply to learn more about human labor.
只是想學習人類的工作內容
But a misunderstanding led to this situation.
卻因為一場誤會 導致這種局面
We're really embarrassed.
實在沒臉見人
I see, I understand everything now.
原來如此 事情我都明白了
She actually understood.
居然明白了
This woman seems to be an incurable do-gooder.
看來這女的是個不得了的濫好人
There was an explosion in the Magic Bureau.
魔導廳發生爆炸
It wasn't what you did, right?
應該不是你們搞的鬼吧
O-Of course not.
當…當然不是
We would never let this girl have something like that in her possession.
讓這女孩拿那種東西太危險了 絕對不會那麼做
I thought you had accidentally set gas on fire
我還以為是妳的火之魔法
or something with your fire magic.
不小心引爆了瓦斯之類的
My flames won't accidentally ignite gas or oil.
我的火焰不會意外引爆 瓦斯或是油類
Because the ability to ignite or extinguish is within my grasp.
因為要燃燒或熄滅 都是由我自己控制
I find myself wanting to recruit her more and more.
越來越想要這個人才了
But if so, that explosion…
但是既然如此 那場爆炸究竟…
Right, I almost forgot to return this to you.
對了 差點忘了還妳
Miss Lim, this is your phone.
琳姆小姐 這是妳的手機
There were many calls when you were asleep.
妳睡著的時候也打來了很多次
CHIEF FRED
(弗雷德長官)
Can I answer it?
我可以接嗎
Sure.
請吧
Hello.
喂
Lim, where are you?
琳姆 妳人在哪裡
I'm very sorry, Chief.
非常抱歉 長官
I was injured in the explosion and passed out.
我在爆炸中受傷 昏了過去
And now…
然後…
Someone is helping me with my injuries.
現在有人在幫我療傷
So you're in the hospital?
所以妳在醫院嗎
No, no, where are you?
不 不對 妳在哪裡
I'm at…
我在…
Just tell the truth, it's okay.
照實說吧 沒關係
I'm at Hero Max's house.
我在勇者麥克斯先生的家裡
Let me talk to him.
叫他聽電話
Fred.
弗雷德
Alright, Max.
好了 麥克斯
Can you please explain in detail?
能不能請你詳細說明一下
Attack a national institution in collaboration with the demon clan.
與魔族勾結 襲擊國家機關
You, the hero, have also fallen.
你這個勇者也墮落了呢
I admit that I have ties to the demon clan.
我承認我和魔族來往
But that explosion wasn't our doing.
但是那場爆炸不是我們做的
Is that so?
是嗎…
But we can pretend it was you.
不過要當成這樣也可以喔
Or rather, it's more convenient for us to treat you as the criminal.
不如說讓你當犯人 辦事更方便
Anyway, I will explain everything.
總之我會一五一十說明
Can we meet?
能見個面嗎
Sure.
可以啊
Just wait at your home, I'll be right there.
在家裡等著 我立刻過去
Remember to tell the demon clans to come out and see me too.
別以為你能藏匿魔族
Alright.
我知道啦
But you must have noticed the presence of the demon clan
不過你上次來我家時
the last time you visited my house.
就察覺到魔族的存在了吧
Why did you suddenly…
為何那時…突然…回…
Who are you?
是誰
LIM, ON CALL Fred, can you hear me?
(琳姆 通話中) 弗雷德 聽得見嗎
What's wrong with you?
怎麼啦
Your house… is a bit too small.
你家待起來很不自在
There's a place I often go to.
有一家我常去的店
I'll have someone take you there, let's meet directly at the shop.
再請人帶你過去 直接約在店裡吧
Don't try to run away.
不准開溜
Okay.
我知道
Right, you wouldn't play such petty tricks.
也是 你才不會耍這種小把戲
GARBLED CHARACTERS, INCOMING CALL
(來電中)
DECLINE
(拒絕)
I am sure you can hear me, right?
明明聽得見吧
Answer the phone!
給我接電話啊
This area is directly beneath the explosion site.
這一帶是爆炸地點的正下方
Everyone, be careful of collapses.
務必當心坍塌
Okay.
好
Someone passed out!
有人倒在地上
-You coward… -It's Chief Fred.
-沒骨氣… -是弗雷德長官
-Did he get caught in the explosion?
-被爆炸波及了嗎
-You coward… -This is bad, start the rescue immediately.
-沒骨氣… -糟了 立刻展開救援
Captain, why did the Magic Bureau explode all of a sudden?
話說回來 隊長 為什麼魔導廳會突然爆炸
I don't know, but if it really was a terrorist attack by the Republic Gamma…
不曉得 但假如真是剛瑪共和國發動恐攻
Things have become serious.
事情就嚴重了
BESKER KINGDOM, CABINET OFFICE BUILDING
(貝斯卡王國 內閣府廳舍)
NINE MINISTERS' MEETING
(九大臣會議)
FOURTH MINISTER, REINHARD What a disaster out of the blue.
(第四大臣 萊因哈德) 真是飛來橫禍
I heard you were in the Magic Bureau at the time.
聽說你當時在魔導廳
THIRD MINISTER, GREMES Yes, I almost got caught in it. Such a headache.
(第三大臣 格雷姆斯) 對啊 差點就被波及 真頭疼
SIXTH MINISTER, HAYWARD Fortunately, you are safe.
(第六大臣 海沃德) 幸好平安無事
But the situation is now quite serious.
然而現在事態相當嚴重
FIRST MINISTER, FRANCA I knew this day would come sooner or later
(第一大臣 法蘭卡) 自從你們趕走雷奧
after you guys drove Leo away.
我就知道遲早會有這麼一天
Isn't this good? We now have a reason to go to war.
這不是挺好的嗎 有了開戰的理由
EIGHTH MINISTER, MENEHERDO That's not what this was about.
(第八大臣 梅涅赫爾多) 現在並不是在打那種算盤
This is obviously a terrorist attack by the Republic.
這次顯然是共和國展開恐攻
EIGHTH MINISTER, MENEHERDO It's a crisis for the kingdom and our people.
(第八大臣 梅涅赫爾多) 使王國與國民面臨危機
FIFTH MINISTER, SEMAN Can't we find a way to put this to rest?
(第五大臣 塞曼) 能不能設法息事寧人呢
SECOND MINISTER, TRIGOLIN Then what do you propose we do?
(第二大臣 特里戈林) 那你說該怎麼做
Should we bow to them and ask them to stop?
向對方低頭 請他們停手嗎
If we go to war, our army will not back down.
若要開戰 我軍不會有一絲猶豫
However, all of our battles up to this point have been for show
然而至今的交戰
and to stake claim to the land.
僅是為了宣揚領有主張 做做樣子
NINTH MINISTER, GEORGE So we have never really clashed
(第九大臣 喬治) 因此免於正式起衝突
and have avoided casualties.
也能避免雙方人員傷亡
NINTH MINISTER, GEORGE But this time, it's different.
(第九大臣 喬治) 但是這次不同了
If the kingdom's army launches a total attack…
如果王國軍出動全部兵力進攻…
He will show his true power.
他將使出真本事
Even if we win, I am afraid we will suffer significant losses.
即使不會敗北 恐怕仍會損失慘重
I don't want to send my men to their deaths.
我不想叫部下送死
"Even if we win"? You really dare to say it.
還敢講"即使不會敗北"
We can't win, which is why we can only pick faults.
就是贏不了 才會故意找碴
You're just a trash soldier. What kind of attitude is that?
區區的垃圾軍人擺什麼架子
You're going too far, Sezac.
說得太過火了 斯茲克
SEVENTH MINISTER, SEZAC Alright, alright, sorry.
(第七大臣 斯茲克) 好啦好啦 抱歉
So, what we need is a force that can compete with Leo.
意思是我們需要 足以與雷奧匹敵的戰力
The only force that can compete with a hero's companion is,
能與勇者同伴抗衡的戰力
of course, a hero's companion.
當然只有勇者的同伴
Gremes,
格雷姆斯
you're pretty close with Fred, right?
你和弗雷德挺親近的吧
Can you handle it? After all, the others are useless.
能不能麻煩你了 畢竟其他傢伙都派不上用場
Oh my.
真是的
I have had a run of bad luck.
抽到了一個下下籤
This restaurant looks very upscale.
這家餐廳看起來很高級
After all, this is the chief's favorite restaurant.
畢竟是長官御用餐廳啊
Shave your beard clean!
把鬍子剃乾淨
Otherwise, we will not be allowed in!
不然會被當作生客 拒絕入內
This is really luxurious.
這還真是奢侈
Do you eat such good food every day? That's scary.
你天天都吃這種好料嗎 真嚇人
I don't eat it every day.
不可能天天吃
Eat it. We haven't dined together in a long time.
吃吧 好久沒有一起用餐了
Lady, please enjoy your meal as well.
同行的小姐也歡迎享用
Thank you so much.
太謝謝了
Wow, Max, look.
好棒喔 麥克斯你看
This sashimi is so clear and translucent.
這個生魚片晶瑩剔透呢
Thank you for the meal.
我開動囉
It's so hard… It's so delicious.
好硬…好好吃
You are powerful demon clans.
是個實力高強的魔族呢
CUSTOMER FIRST And almost perfectly disguised as humans.
而且幾乎完美偽裝成人類
I had no idea such dangerous demon clans still existed.
想不到還有如此危險的魔族倖存
Is her name Zenia?
是叫潔妮亞嗎
Is that glasses demon clan your subordinate?
那個眼鏡魔族是妳的部下嗎
Yes.
是的
Sorry, Fred.
對不起 弗雷德
We have really caused you a lot of trouble.
真的給你添了很大的麻煩
I am very sorry.
十分抱歉
Anyway, you seem to be enjoying it. That's great too.
反正你看起來挺享受的 也不錯
After all, no human woman will be looking at you right now.
畢竟現在沒有人類女性會理你
Even though you are a hero.
明明是勇者
Mind your own business.
要你管
But I really envy you that
不過真羨慕你
you get to live with two beautiful women.
生活周遭就有兩位美女
It's embarrassing.
人家會害羞啦
I wonder what he would think if he knew his true identity.
要是他知道真實身分 不知會怎麼想
Anyway,
總之我必須好好澄清一下
I need to clarify the explosion at Magic Bureau…
你那邊魔導廳的爆炸案…
I know it wasn't what you did.
我知道那不是出自你們之手
Zenia left traces everywhere
潔妮亞從屋頂入侵魔導廳之後
after infiltrating the Magic Bureau from the roof.
在各處都留下了行蹤痕跡
Even if she is stupid, she will not be wandering around
如果是她裝的炸彈
inside the building if she planted the bomb, right?
再怎麼蠢 也不會在建築內部閒晃吧
I-I see.
這…這樣啊
So you understand. You're really sensible.
你都知道嗎 果然明事理
Thank you. Friends are there for when you're in trouble.
謝謝你 有難就是要靠朋友
Enough said.
別說了
So this matter is settled then.
那麼這件事就此解決了吧
Thanks for the meal. See you next time.
感謝招待 下次見
Don't leave.
別走
I won't interfere this time.
這次的事情我不過問
Consequently, you're responsible for the aftermath.
相對的 要請你幫忙收拾殘局
Um… Maybe you could spend the night with the woman. How is it?
這…不然那女人 隨你處置一整晚 如何
A-Are you joking?
開…開什麼玩笑
What are you thinking, Max? You're a menace to women!
你在想什麼 麥克斯 簡直是女性公敵
Should you really say that as a hero?
身為勇者 你說這種話沒問題嗎
Let us cut to the chase, Zenia is your subordinate, right?
追根究柢 潔妮亞是你的部下吧
When a subordinate makes a mistake, the superior should take responsibility.
部下犯錯 當然要由上司承擔責任
F-Fine, I guess there's no choice.
好…好吧 沒辦法
I will serve you until you are satisfied…
朕會服務你 直到滿意為止…
I don't need it! Put your clothes back on!
不需要 把衣服穿上
I have serious matters to discuss. Sit down, both of you.
我要談正事了 坐下
Okay.
好
Don't you need my naked body?
不需要朕脫光光嗎
We are officially going to war with Republic Gamma.
要正式與剛瑪共和國開戰了
Who told those idiots to commit such a stupid act as a bomb terror attack?
誰叫那群傢伙要做出 炸彈恐攻這種蠢事
Was it really the Republic who did it?
那個真是共和國做的嗎
Of course, who else could it be?
當然 不然會是誰
Who knows.
天曉得
I just thought the explosion was a bit lackluster.
我只是覺得那種爆炸太寒酸了
What do you mean by that, Max?
這話是什麼意思 麥克斯
Nothing.
沒什麼
Max.
麥克斯
You think I really want to go to war with the Republic?
你是不是覺得 我巴不得跟共和國開戰
How could that be possible?
那怎麼可能
Quite the opposite.
完全相反
If you are willing to assist the Kingdom, I would be very happy.
如果你願意協助王國 我會很高興的
But it doesn't matter if you don't want to help.
但不肯協助也無所謂
I can avoid a full-fledged conflict with the Republic
只要把爆炸案的罪行 推到你和那些魔族身上
as long as I can blame you and those demon clans for the explosion.
也能暫時避免 與共和國發生全面衝突
Personally, I'm fine with either.
我個人是兩者都可以
This is your ultimatum.
這是最後通牒
Make your choice again.
你重新做個選擇吧
Fight for the kingdom, return as a hero.
要為了王國挺身而戰 回來當勇者
Or you can be an accomplice to the demon clans
還是成為魔族的共犯
and end up as a major criminal.
以極大罪人的身分結束人生
I am suddenly irritated!
突然覺得麻煩死啦
I might as well move.
乾脆搬家好了
Move to the Republic Gamma with her.
跟她一起搬去剛瑪共和國
What did you just say?
什麼
The hot springs there are really great.
泡溫泉泡得真舒服
The Republic Gamma is a good place.
剛瑪共和國真是個好地方
You agree, right?
對吧
Let's leave this country with its strong smell of gunpowder behind
早點離開這個火藥味濃厚的國家
and lead a leisurely life, soaking in hot springs!
過著悠哉的泡溫泉人生也不錯
It wouldn't be bad at all, plus there's an abundant magical ore vein there,
還有豐沛的魔礦脈
so we might still make a fortune from it in the future!
那裡以後還會賺進大把金子吧
I can't just pretend I didn't hear that.
這番話我可不能當作沒聽到
You're declaring yourself a terrorist.
你等於是聲明自己是恐怖分子
You will become a complete enemy of the kingdom.
將完全與王國為敵
That's right.
就是啊
Don't make an enemy of the great hero who defeated the Demon Lord.
不想跟打倒魔王的 偉大勇者大人為敵吧
So when you ask me for a favor, show more sincerity.
那拜託人家時要拿出更多誠意
Stop being so narcissistic.
少自戀了
You can't call yourself a hero in your current state.
現在的你哪能自稱勇者
You're just a powerful and troublesome NEET.
只是個擁有麻煩力量的尼特族罷了
I'm angry! I'm furious! I'm moving right now!
我生氣了 超火大 現在就搬家
I'm moving to the Republic Gamma!
搬到剛瑪共和國
The Republic would refuse to accept
像你這種大型垃圾
a large piece of trash like you!
共和國也會拒絕接收好嗎
Wake up, you fool!
清醒點 你這個呆瓜
Stop it…
你們別吵了…
Shut up! You're the big fool!
吵死了 你才是大呆瓜
All you do is cause pointless disputes!
只會搞一堆無謂的紛爭
You can keep fighting until you drop dead! Don't drag me into it!
吵到死為止吧 不要拉我下水
We must end these pointless disputes! How do you not understand this?
我是要終結這些無謂的紛爭 你怎麼就是不懂
Let you fools kill each other as you please!
隨便你們這群蠢貨盡情自相殘殺
As long as you and Leo are dead,
只要你跟雷奧都翹辮子
my ears will finally have some peace!
耳根就清淨多了
You bastard!
你這個混蛋
Stop it!
別吵了
Let me go.
放開我
Max, who is this demon clan?
麥克斯 這個魔族是誰
None of your business. We're leaving.
跟你無關吧 我們要回去了
Don't think this is the end.
別以為這樣就結束了
Your powers are too troublesome.
你們的力量太礙事
If we can't control…
如果不能控制…
Right, I didn't bring any money today. I'll leave the bill to you.
對了 我今天一毛錢也沒帶 交給你買單囉
After all, you're paying with taxpayers' money.
反正是用稅金付的吧
I should have poisoned the drink.
早知道就在裡面下毒
We're back.
回來啦
Don't just throw your clothes anywhere, Max.
衣服脫了不可以亂丟 麥克斯
This one is a rare formal outfit.
這件可是難得的正式服裝
Welcome back.
歡迎回來
Max, what's wrong with you?
麥克斯 你怎麼了
Could it be…
難…難不成…
Damn it, I've been set up.
該死的 被擺了一道
I feel relieved.
朕放心了
I thought you were really poisoned.
還以為你真的被下毒了
Laxatives are almost as bad as poison.
瀉藥跟毒差不多吧
That bastard.
那個混蛋
He probably put it in your drink from the start.
大概是一開始 就在你的酒裡下藥了吧
If I had agreed to his terms, what would he have done?
如果我答應了他的要求 他要怎麼辦啊
Perhaps he knew you would never agree.
或許他明白你絕不會答應吧
It's probably retaliation for the Zenia incident.
八成是針對潔妮亞那件事報復
ESTIMATED TO HAVE BEEN A REPUBLIC GAMMA TERRORIST ATTACK MAGIC BUREAU EXPLOSION INCIDENT
(判定是剛瑪共和國恐攻) (魔導廳爆炸案)
That's ridiculous. I can't believe they're doing this.
太扯了 居然耍這種花招
Those guys are too despicable.
那群傢伙太卑鄙了
It's rotten to the core.
腐敗至極
Captain, we swear we didn't launch a terror attack.
團長 我們敢發誓 絕對沒有發動恐攻
I know.
我知道
They seem to be serious.
他們似乎想來真的
I no longer consider that place to be my homeland
以為耍這種手段管用的話
if they believe that such measures will succeed.
那我也不把那裡當祖國了
If they dare, let them come.
要來就來吧